…is we’re going to have to automate faster.
I don’t know if this automation can happen quickly enough.
The meat facilities are right now running under capacity.
Beef is up about 24%, depending on which article you read.
Much of it is due, you can say, because of packer control,
but also because of the human hands that touch our meat in the facilities.
Can we automate fast enough?
To do so, I believe that we’re going to see
more ag innovation come from outside agriculture.
What if the new innovation is beyond just giving an engineer a task
and they change it 10%, but instead they change it 100%?
Innovation will come to this industry from outside,
and we need to embrace it, not reject it.
Because innovation that comes to agriculture might be from
a completely different, 180-degree position, and you’ll say,
“Holy crap, I can’t believe we didn’t do that.”
Uber and Lyft were not founded by the CEO of Yellow Cab, were they?
And I’m telling you what, I’m opposed to it.
When I was a kid at Northwest Elementary School,
I remember the day that the policeman came in there in kindergarten.
The first thing he said was, “Children, don’t ever get into a car with strangers.”
Now it’s a business.
Think about that. You are told from the time you’re a kid,
“Don’t get in a car with a stranger.”
Now it’s just to hop in a car when somebody pulls up and says,
“Are you Damian?” “No.”
They can’t get your name right. I hop in a car with them.
Makes no sense to me.